Hello high school sophomore, I'm 16 years old and I'm Serizamar, please.
I'd like to share with you some of the clothes I bought with you.
The first one is this hoodie!
The fabric of this hoodie is very strong and I think it's a lucky material for winter, and the design of this hoodie is very cute.
The design of this hoodie is so cute!
The back of the hoodie says "more inside than on your face".
It's not hidden by the hat.
It's not hidden by the hat, and I think it's a cute design even at a quick glance.
I think these bottoms will go with anything, so please try them with your favorite bottoms.
Now, let's look at the second item.
The second item is a knit with arm covers.
Arm covers are very popular this year, and I've seen a lot of influencers wearing them, so I've been curious about them.
I was also interested in this knit set because it is made of the same material as the knit set, and since it is black, I thought it would be easy to match with other items.
I'm wearing it to a lesson right now, but I think it's really easy to match with anything.
If it were me, I would wear black shorts or black pants.
I think it would be cute with black shorts or black shorts.
So, here's a photo shoot of the shopping!
So here we go!
Good morning!
Today, I have three daughters.
I actually have three daughters.
My eldest daughter is an idol in the entertainment industry.
She is an idol in the entertainment industry.
I go to her live performances often, but I have never shown my daughters' existence on youtube, my instagram, or anywhere else. I'd like to introduce you to Moua Serizawa of Ukka, a member of Stardust Panettes, please.
We're a group of six and we usually perform as idols.
We're working really hard so please check out our profile page.
Please support us!
We are going to make our major debut on November 16th, so please look forward to hearing from us.
Let's go shopping now, shall we?
What do you think?
Do you recognize Sanrio from somewhere?
Sanrio? I know, I know.
I want to go to Sanrio once.
I've been really into it lately.
I don't know where that is.
I want to go to Sanrio one time.
Did you see it?
Yeah, I looked it up.
Oh, yeah?
I don't know.
I'm into Sanrio.
Yeah, I only knew about Sanrio before.
But I've recently decided on a favorite character.
I see.
I collect a lot.
Use the time.
You always shop alone.
I do most of my shopping...
Almost always by myself.
I tend to go in between jobs.
I always end up at the same stores.
I just go in.
But I know what I'm going to do, so I just hurry up and get out.
Oh, I see.
Really?
Do you go shopping for clothes by yourself?
All the time.
Yes, and lately I've been shopping online.
I see.
Yeah, I'm the type of person who can't sleep at all at night.
At night, I get the urge to buy things.
I often buy things.
I see.
But aren't you afraid to buy online? Sizes and stuff.
My mom says I should just get a size small. So...
Can I get a small?
Yeah.
I was also wondering if I could lend it to my sister or something.
What? Where is it?
Oh? Where are your other clothes?
Clothes...
Where are the clothes?
I don't know, something a little more grown-up?
Uh-huh.
Oh, I like it.
I don't know if it's a mature day.
Yes, I like it.
Lately I've been able to buy my own clothes without relying on my mom.
Before, I would go to the store with her and she would definitely take care of me once.
But recently I've been able to buy things without permission, and sometimes people say, "What's with these clothes?But lately I've been able to buy them without permission, but sometimes people say, what's with these clothes?
Oh, so that's how it is. I couldn't choose my own clothes until now.
But now I can choose, and sometimes I get compliments, and sometimes I get "what's that?
Oh, I see.
Oh, there it is.
Isn't this it?
Where is Sanryo?
I'm here now.
Okay, well, we'll just keep looking.
Why don't we go to Zara?
Do you have any idea what kind of clothes would look good on me?
I don't know. I think I'd look good in anything.
Really?
Really. Yeah, I'm sure. I think I look good in everything.
I have a theme of wanting to look mature,
If I make a mistake, I look like my mom,
I'm often told that I look like an office worker in the interior.
I've become too mature.
Yes, that's right. I feel like it's me.
But I feel like I'm getting taller and taller every time I fit in.
Not really.
It stopped.
Stopped?
Yes, I stopped at 160.
Oh, you're 160?
That's right. But my sister is the second biggest among her siblings.
Oh, that's right.
That's right.
So, do you want to see? Zara? I will.
Zara is kind of cute, but I'm not ready to try...
I'll look at it, but there are clothes I can't try on, so I'd like to look at it. I see.
But I look at it a lot. I'm totally comfortable looking at it.
That's OK.
But it's winter now. Yes, yes, yes.
I'd like to wear winter clothes.
I like blouses...blouses...blouses...blouses...blouses...blouses...blouses...blouses...I saw one that was really beautiful.
I'm sure she'll remember how beautiful it is.
Oh, I see... I'm wearing super-thick flooring, so it makes me look even bigger.
You can buy anything you like.
Buy whatever you want.
I think this one is cute.
I thought you'd look cute with this belt.
I'm a girl.
For example, I really have no sense of fashion.
Oh, really?
I really don't have any fashion sense.
But it's okay, right? You look cute.
Cute?
I think it's cute. You mean they're sold as a set, right?
Maybe a set? I saw them together.
I don't have the thick belt, but I like it.
Oh, I see what you mean. It's attached. I don't know.
I don't know. They're attached.
It's cute.
Is it cute?
Is there one?
Maybe it's the one on the back.
This one? No.
Maybe this one? Maybe.
That one? That's it, right? Is that it? That's not it.
This one? What is it?
Oh, that's it!
This one's cute.
And this one and this one.
Can I get a basket?
You want me to grab a basket?
I'm still thinking about it, but I haven't bought it yet.
I don't know what I'm gonna do.
You should buy them, but you should listen to what the other girls say.
I'll buy it then.
I'm a little curious.
Also, my sisters have been really craving Korean gummies and stuff lately, so have them take a look.
Oh, yeah! Why don't you just buy them for them?
Yeah.
Have you ever tried Earth gummies?
Yes! Aren't they good?
You've never had them?
No?
They're delicious.
We seem to be out of Earth gummies.Earth gummies seem to be pretty much out of stock.
I guess they don't have Earth, they've turned into soccer balls.
They only have soccer balls?
I might have said I like these.
I like these.
Can I have two?
Sure.
Popcorn?
Do you eat a lot of candy? Usually.
I also eat s'mores. I like dried mango.
Oh, you like it.
Yeah, I love it.
I'd eat it too if I had some.
Really? Thank you. We're the same.
Yeah, we were.
We're very similar.
Do you like dried bananas?
I like dried bananas.
I know. I like s'mores, too.
I also like dried plums.
We all eat dried plums.
That's about all the snacks.
Is this enough candy?
Thank you.
Yes, I bought a lot of things at the Plaza.
My sisters are interested in some Korean snacks, so I bought some for them as well.
Thank you very much.
No, no, no, it's no problem at all.
Let's move on to the next store.
Yes, I'm going.
Yes, but not Sanrio,
There are characters, right?
And I'm afraid my second sister and I might guess the same one.
I'm sure I'm going to get the same one.
Oh, I see.
That's why I changed it.
But you know what?
I didn't know you could be into Sanrio at your age.
At my age?
Yeah.
No, not me.
Moa.
Well, it's something,
I've always liked the second one,
Oh, I see.
I was wondering why you liked it.
But now I get it. It's kind of cute.
Also, it's fun to collect them when they're all snuggled up.
Oh, really?
Girls don't really have guys,
I mean, there are guys I like, of course, but..,
That's why I've been..,
Like, Oni Sekai,
One Piece, and so on,
I've seen many things,
I've never liked any of them,
Well, I like to watch them,
but I've never thought of collecting them.
Oh, I see.
Because if there was something related to it
You would collect anything related to it, right?
Yes, that's right.
That's great.
If it's a character.
But on the other hand, I don't watch anime at all.
I don't watch anime or dramas at all,
Oh, really?
I've never watched any Sanrio cartoons either,
But, you know, I like things.
Hee...
I see.
Sanrio has an anime.
Eh, I heard there's something about it.
Heh.
So you wanted to go to Sanrio for the time being.
Yes, I wanted to see it once.
Oh, there it is, there it is. Snoopy is not Sanrio, right?
No, it's not.
I came to the Sanrio goods section. I like it, so I want to take a look.
I'm looking for Pochacco. Here is Pochacco.Look for Pochacco. This is Pochacco.
I saw it for the first time. I thought I was imagining this one. This is Pom-Pom Pudding. But she is also a very popular character.
Oh, yeah.
Yes, um...
Um, uh, explain the key.
It's done. Um, I drew the lottery for Puchocco.
And I won a face towel.
Cute.
I won a face towel.
Yes, I'm lucky.
I'm lucky.
Yes.
Oh, it's okay, I'll put it in.
Thank you.
I was also interested in this ring for my phone, so I bought it.
I'll put it on.
But WEGO has quite a few things that both women and men could wear.
WEGO bought me these arm covers that are all the rage these days.
Arm covers.
The ones that are open only here.
I bought the ones that tan only here.
What do you want to do?
Do you want to see something else?
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
What do you want to eat?
Uh, something clean.
I'd like something non-staining.
Except pasta.
Are you hungry? How hungry?
How hungry am I?
But I can eat.
I'm not really hungry, but I can eat.
Oh, okay.
Well, do you want to grab a bite to eat?
Yeah, sure.
I was at Matsuya this morning...
Matsuya?
At Matsuya, I had the...
I had the salmon set meal.
Oh, I see.
Yes, I love salmon so much, I had the salmon set meal.
You like salmon?
I like salmon.
You like salmon? Oh, we're the same.
It's really delicious.
It is.
What do you like? Favorite food. Basically, I like yakiniku.
Yakiniku? Yakiniku. But it's delicious, isn't it?
That's the first time I've heard that answer. Seriously?
Well, you like crab, right? I like crab.
But there's no such thing as clean food.
Oh, I see.
The only clean food is mayonnaise and pickles.
Oh, you can't eat pickles.
But you can eat cucumbers and eggplants these days.
Oh, pickles?
Yes.
If you can eat pickled eggplant, isn't that a big improvement?
No, I can't eat pickled radishes.
No?
No.
huh?
What do you want?
What do you think?
Well, Korean food is popular, so Korean food is a possibility.
But I don't know how I look.
I like Japanese food.
I saw some Japanese food over there.
I'll eat it.
This is very Japanese food.
Looks delicious!
Do you like Japanese food? Japanese food.
Wait.
Yes, I do. Iced tea?
Is this it?
Yes, that's it.
Here's one.One of these.
Because.
White rice, please.
And this for Hirazu.
Yes, I'll have some.
I, silk is...
Yes.
Thank you for your service.
Yes, thank you.
Excuse me.
This rice is in place of miso soup.
Yes, thank you.
Thank you for using our service.
Thank you very much.
The announcer will be sending a response, so please be careful.
Yes, thank you.
Bon appétit.
I can't eat tea and salad.
Oh, I see.
And pickles.
Do you eat breakfast? Every day.
Almost never.
I tend to have it for lunch.
Twice a day.
I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know if I'm done growing up,
When I was growing up, I ate 30 solid meals,
Nowadays, I don't eat, but I don't have to.
If I eat in the morning, is it bread? Rice?
Rice.
I'm a rice person.
I'm kind of hoping for rice.
But even if there is bread, I try not to eat much.
I don't know...
When I was little, I used to want to eat only bread for breakfast.
Remember that?
Yeah, I remember.
That's why I thought kids these days don't eat rice, but nowadays they do.
Well, I don't know what it is, but if there is salmon, salmon set meal, and bread, I definitely want salmon.
If there was rice, I would eat it.
Yeah, I'd eat it if there was rice.
It's true that we all eat it.
You two eat it too?
They eat bread.
Oh, I see.
They don't seem like food lovers to me.
I don't think so.
I don't think they like to eat fish either.
Oh, I'll eat that.
Mom, you know, ever since Noah was really little...
What? She always told us to eat quickly.
She told the three of us to eat quickly.
Yeah, she did.
She did? I'm sure she did.
That's why we all eat so fast.
Oh, I see.
You eat fast?
Yeah.
You're a fast eater.
The fastest of them all.
Really?
Yeah.
I eat really fast, too.
I don't like to spend too much time on my food.
That's true.
Yeah, it's a waste of time.
time eating.
Yeah.
Even if I go out to eat to kill time, I'm done eating in about 15 minutes, so it doesn't pass the time at all.
I have this image of women.
For example, you go to Starbucks and buy coffee, right?
I don't want to drink a lot of coffee. I want to take something with me.
I drink it in half a day or something, well, not half a day, but there are people who drink it for a while, and I drink it all at once.
I drink a lot of tapioca, but I'm probably that type.
I drink it all at once until I'm almost done, and then I'm done.
He's the tallest guy.
You know how the other day when I came home, I said "I'm home"?
And you saw him in the shadows.
I thought he was huge.It's huge.
Oh, it's, like, 64?
I think so.
When the three of us were standing in a row.
One of us was taller than the other.
And he plays volleyball, so he's in good shape.
But since we're not really that different, we're kind of playing "who's taller?
How's it going? How's work going?
Uka's major label debut is coming up on November 16th.
A major label debut?
That's right.
And the first one-man live performance after the major debut
December 21 at a place called Sausage & Club in Yokohama.
Is that right?
That's right.
November 21.
You came to see this?
Yeah, come.
It's something, isn't it?
The last time you saw me live...
The nativity?
It was my 6 year old's birthday.
A year?
A year? Yeah.
Yeah. That time, too.
The Corona was pretty bad.
There was a lot of space between seats.
Lately I've been going to my sister's shows.
To some extent.
Yeah, pretty good.
You get to see everyone up close.
I'm looking forward to going again.
After her major label debut.
I'll be in front of you at the group shows.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, pretty close. For a group?
What was that? When was the last time we went as a group?
Oh, that...
That's when my sister and I went to see them.
That's right. When I was in eighth grade.
Shinjuku.
We took pictures. Shinjuku.
You were in eighth grade?
Three years ago.
Really? That long ago?
I think you've grown up.
That long ago?
That's right.
I'm singing and dancing as hard as I can right now.
I'm doing my best. Please support me.
I'm Uka.
Live concerts...
We have a summer concert coming up.
Well...
If we have that...
I'm going to release the album, so I'm going to have a lot of events for the release.
If there are any near you, please come and see us!
Please come and see us.
So, that was about three hours.
We had a good time shopping and eating lunch.
I bought quite a few things.
I bought a lot of things I was interested in, and I thought they were cute.
It was really fun.
So, as I've mentioned many times before,
I've told you many times before that I introduced my daughter to you all,
My daughter's group will be working hard as we prepare for our major label debut,
I hope you will all give me your support.
I'm Uka.
I've put all the details in the summary section,
Please check it out.
Well, I'm going to take you home now.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
Can I do one last thing?
It's my greeting.
Sure, sure.
It's called Byblon.
Byblon?
Sure, let's do it.Okay, let's do it at all.
Let's do it, Vaibyron!
Thank you all for watching!
I am seriously building a campground on my personal channel called OTOUYUKI!
I will be posting many more videos in the future.
Please subscribe to my personal channel!